Mayur Sakhiya

Over 8 years of IT industry experience as a Mobile application developer in the field of Android, los and Flutter. Solid understanding of full mobile development life cycles, UIX, app analytics, and Agile methodologies. Dedicated to continuously developing,

215, S.V.Square, New Ranip, Ahmedabad (+91) 91738 97238 mayursakhiya1@gmail.com

EXPERIENCE

VMV Infosoft, Ahmedabad — *Mobile Tech Lead*

APRIL 2021 - PRESENT

Implemented features for various applications in Java, Kotlin, Dart and Swift Language

Collaborated with quality engineers, user research, product management, design, and support teams to ensure quality in all phases of app development.

eSense Learning Pvt Ltd, Ahmedabad — *Sr Mobile App developer*

MAY 2016 - APRIL 2021

Worked closely with core technology teams and other platform teams to balance cross-platform consistency with Android optimization.

Worked with a team of 5 members and provided end-to-end solutions for clients

Nimblechapps Ltd, Ahmedabad — Android developer

JULY 2015 - JUNE 2016

Designed and developed more than 7 mobile apps live on the Play Store.

Worked with BLE, NFC, beacons, and connected devices.

Softqube Technologies Pvt Ltd, Ahmedabad — Android developer

FEB 2013 - JUNE 2015

Worked with GPS, Map, Xmpp, and school management systems.

Established a team of 3 people covering every key role in an early-stage startup.

SKILLS

Flutter & Dart

Android Development

Java

Kotlin

Architecture Pattern

Version Control Systems (Git)

Design pattern

Architecture components

GraphQL and REST APIs

Firebase database

push notifications

LANGUAGES

English, Hindi, Gujarati

EDUCATION

Sunshine College, Rajkot — *Master of Computer Application*

MAY 2010 - APRIL 2013

Gujarat Technological University.

G.K & C.K Bosamia College, Jetpur — Bachelor of Commerce

MONTH 2007 - MONTH 2010

Saurashtra University.

PROJECTS

Kemnu — *Hangouts*

- Engagement marketplace for students and organizations
- Request to Join events
- Chat with all the people attending the event
- Earn rewards by making new friends and participating in hangouts

Imageva— Bussiness Template

- Business promotion with Daily Quote on attractive graphic templates.
- Dynamic UI of graphics template change
- Payment option with subscription-based plans

TopScorer— Online Education Learning

- TopScorer is a learning app that provides Audiovisual, MCQs, learning notes, Al-based assessments and easy to understand analytics
- Online video streaming with the track of student activity
- Payment option for purchasing a pack of learning courses